Excuse me, ma'am.
Yes?
Question for you.
Hey, I know who you are.
Yeah?
Yeah, you're that handsome guy, but
what are you doing in this jacket?
I gotta ask you real quick.
How old were you when you became a millionaire?
And what's the most amount of money
that you've ever made in one year?
$66 million cash.
And I haven't spent it.
Yeah?
You made that in a year?
No, I made that in a day.
You made that in one day?
How?
Yes, I did.
I sold the business.
I built the Corcoran Group,
and that's what they paid me.
Now, I came all the way up to New York
City to ask you how you got rich and how somebody
watching can become rich in today's world.
Could we interview you for a minute real quick?
Yeah, but how about we interview inside?
It's a little cold out today.
Do you mind?
Is that okay?
Yeah, I was just in my office.
Okay.
How can somebody become a multimillionaire in today's world?
I would say...
You guys, we just got to New York City,
and we're about to go meet up with and interview
one of the most iconic New York
City entrepreneurs of all time, Barbara Corcoran.
A lot of you guys have seen her
on Shark Tank, where she's investing millions of dollars
into businesses.
But a lot of you guys don't know
that she herself is a New York City businesswoman.
She's a mogul.
In fact, a couple years ago, she
sold a business for over $60 million.
So we're going to go meet up with Barbara
and go figure out how she got rich, her secrets
to becoming financially free, and how you
can become wealthy just like Barbara in today's
world.
So let's go meet up with Barbara
and go see what she has to say.
Come on.
Awesome.
Barbara.
So nice to meet you.
My mother.
James.
We should get that coat.
Pretty sassy.
I think I got it from Zara.
Thank you so much.
I appreciate that.
They have the best coats.
They do have some good coats.
High-low.
A lot of girls shop there.
I don't even have a
good taste enough to shop there.
Thank you for allowing us to
come out here and interview you.
We really appreciate it.
I had no choice.
You said you were coming over.
Yeah.
We're huge fans of yours,
so it means a lot, really.
We really appreciate that.
You're doing a great job.
Thank you.
How do you see it?
I love your Shaquille O'Neal.
You like Shaq?
I watch it like five times.
I'm just locked on him.
I wish he was my husband.
Yeah?
You like Shaq?
I love him, and he loves me.
Yeah, I love that.
That's awesome.
But you know what?
I said, he did such a great job.
I have to be better than him.
I am competitive.
Yeah, I love that.
I love that.
That's awesome.
Who am I here with today?
Barbara Corcoran.
And for those that don't know, what industry
did you decide to pursue a career in?
Real estate all the way, but I've
recently been a shark on Shark Tank.
All different industries.
How did you even get on the Shark Tank?
How does that work?
What was that process?
Oh, that was a weird, weird ride.
Well, I got chosen for Shark Tank.
I signed the contract for Shark Tank.
I got fired by Shark Tank, and I lost my
seat and regained it before the first day I was
on the set.
It was a rollercoaster ride.
How'd you regain it?
I'm good at persuading people.
I wrote the producer a vivid email
and told him he had made a mistake.
I thought his rejection was a lucky charm,
that everything in my life that was a rejection
was a lucky charm, and he should invite
both ladies out to compete for the seat.
And I won the seat.
Now, you were also business partners with Donald Trump.
Yes, I was.
And I saw in an interview-
Well, not really business partners.
I worked a lot with the man.
But I saw in an interview, you
said that he was one of the
greatest salesperson, or he was the
greatest salesperson that you ever saw.
Yeah.
What did you learn from doing business with him?
I learned that bullshit flies if you're selling.
It's okay.
People will believe it.
That's what I learned from Donald Trump.
Were you a good saleswoman?
I was a phenomenal salesperson.
I made most of the money in
my company, but I didn't want to.
The key to really getting ahead, like
Shaquille said, not to quote him, delegation.
I love when he said that.
That's the key.
You were good at bringing people in.
I'm great at hiring the right people, motivating
the right people, getting them to climb mountains
for me and loving me all
along the way and kissing my ass.
Come on.
I'm good at people.
I actually, I wanted to go back to that one.
You said that it's okay for
bullshit to fly a little bit.
Can you kind of break that
one down a little bit more?
Oh, with the Donald Trump?
Yeah.
I learned from him that you could really just
say what you want and somebody in the room
is going to believe it.
I used to think you had to be really buttoned
up and good at what you were saying and state
it exactly as it is.
I learned from him, you don't
have to say it like it is.
People will buy it.
Now, let's say you have a prospective
client who maybe they're on the fence.
We're either leaning towards a no.
How do you get them over to a yes?
What was your secret to sales?
Part of it is I took the
deal away, which is good because everybody always
wants what they can't get their hands on.
I would just say, gee, I'm so sorry.
I heard somebody just took it.
All of a sudden, they want the property.
I would investigate what the offers were and
let them know that there were offers on the
property.
Urgency is a great motivator.
And most importantly, I would listen to what
they said they wanted and I would read between
the lines and know what they really wanted.
Because buyers are liars.
They don't mean to be, but
they don't really tell the truth.
And it's your job as a real estate
agent, any middle guy making a deal, any negotiation
to figure out the truth of the deal.
And like you said, you kind of
have to be a real estate agent.
Yeah.
To take some of that deal away.
You don't have to, but I found it was
a very good trick to take the deal away.
Now, at your business, throughout your career, what
was the most amount of money that you
made in a single year?
$66 million in a day.
In one day?
What happened that day?
It was a good day.
I sold the Corker Group
and I made $66 million cash.
I put it in my checking account.
So you sold a business for $66 million.
Yeah, felt good.
Now, as somebody who exited a business for
over $60 million, you've been at the table
with some very heavy hitters.
What is your best negotiation
advice for anybody in business?
You've got to learn.
You've got to learn to listen.
People are so busy talking, they miss the whole game.
The harder you listen, the better
you are to make a deal.
Is there anything specifically that you're looking
for to be able to ask them questions
about?
Could you kind of explain that?
Because you hear a lot of successful people, they
all say, we've got two ears and one mouth,
so we've got to listen.
What are you listening for exactly?
I'm really always listening for the motivation.
If you get to the motivation of a deal,
you can make the deal because you know what the
real secret is, what pieces
you have to put in place.
If you don't know what's
motivating that guy, it's just guesswork.
Also, timing is so important.
I remember I almost sold my
business one year for $2 million.
I turned it down.
But two years later, I
sold my business for $66 million.
Timing is everything.
Same business, same principle.
Guys, this interview with Barbara has been incredible.
And we're about to get right back to the interview.
But before we do that, I
have a question to ask you.
Are you struggling right now
in your business or your career?
Are you in the exact same position, the exact
same place now that you were six months ago,
a year from now, maybe even a couple years ago?
You need to have realized this sentence right here.
Nothing changes if nothing changes.
If you are still getting advice from the same
people you have been for years that are not
in the places that you want to
be, you are never going to become successful.
But a lot of you guys may
ask, how do I actually find a mentor?
How do I get around people that are
in the places that you want to be?
Well, I have something for you.
So a couple of months ago, I launched and
built what has now become the greatest and the
number one community in the entire
world for business owners and aspiring entrepreneurs.
And you can see right here, guys, we're
the number one community for business, money and
entrepreneurship.
On the school platform.
And the reason why we're the number one community
is because every single week I bring in the
multimillionaires and the billionaires that I interview
on this channel to directly mentor you
and answer all of your questions about your
career, your business, how to start and scale that
company, how to market, how to sell.
For example, I've had the CEO of 7-Eleven
come in and mentor our community and answer your
questions.
I've had Myron Golden, one of the most
iconic salesmen and digital marketers of all time, come
in and mentor our community.
How about even Steven Klubeck, the billionaire that
sold his company for two point two billion
dollars to Hilton?
Guys, if you want to learn directly from millionaires and billionaires like
this every week to help you grow your business, to help you
leave that nine to five, to help you
learn every skill that you need to become successful.
Waste no more time.
Go down to the link in the description of this
video and you can join the community today for free.
Come check it out.
Come get mentored from a millionaire or a billionaire.
I can't wait to see you on the inside.
But with that being said,
let's get back to the video.
And that's another thing, because you hear a lot
of successful people talk about how important timing is.
What told you to wait to exit that business?
Because you could have taken a couple million
dollars and been comfortable for quite a while.
For a year or two.
That's about it.
Yeah.
What were you looking for in the market that told you, you know what,
I'm going to wait and I'm going to exit this thing for way more.
More money.
I was looking for more money.
If they had offered me 66
million, I would have sold it then.
But they didn't.
They offered two million.
You started out in the real estate business with a
thousand dollar loan and you turned it into an absolute empire.
What was your secret to creating wealth in real estate?
Looking back at your career, going back to when you were starting out at 21
years old, what was your formula that you used to accumulate wealth in real estate?
I had a vision that I was going
to be the queen of New York real estate.
I could see it. I could touch it.
I knew what color it was.
I knew what clothes I was wearing.
I could see it in living color.
And it was always my guide.
And I just believed it would happen.
I just believed it would happen the whole time.
How did you find that self-belief
to go make millions of dollars?
Because a lot of people, they doubt themselves.
They struggle with kind
of overcoming those limiting beliefs.
How did you find that self-belief?
Well, I had 22 jobs and I knew if it
didn't work out, I could always get my old job back.
So that's pretty good.
And I knew it was pretty happy poor.
So that was no big deal.
But I think, I think I just saw it.
I dreamed and I saw
it and I just believed it.
I don't know.
Maybe I shouldn't have, but I did.
Now, were you primarily focusing on
residential, commercial or what was your vehicle?
All residential in my business, yeah.
Why residential?
Because residential people need a place to live.
I felt there was always a need for it.
And through highs and lows in the New York
City marketplace, people always needed a place to live.
So I figured I could always make a buck.
So in 2025, what do you think is the best
part of real estate people should be looking to buy?
Let's say a young person, they've got
a hundred grand put to the side.
They want to start making that money work for them.
Where would you put that money in today's world?
I would put it in a two-family house,
live in half-fin, get the other people, the suckers,
paying the rent and paying off the mortgage.
You know, I think it's very
important to get in the game early.
I tried to get in
the game when I was 27.
I bought a studio in Greenwich Village and in a
month I got scared and I purposely failed the board.
Do you know it took me eight
years to catch up to the market?
I couldn't afford the market.
You have to get in the game
early so you have a trade up on.
Now, there's that saying that concentration builds wealth.
Hey, can you slow down a little?
Yeah, yeah, I got you.
I got you.
I'm coming rapid fire.
No, I'm kidding.
You're rapid fire for sure.
It works.
This is amazing though.
So there's a saying that concentration
builds wealth and diversification keeps it.
At what point do you think an entrepreneur should diversify?
Or are you just a proponent?
Of just going deep and
going all in on one thing?
I don't really believe in that bullshit
of diversification because it doesn't work for me.
I do what I do well.
I, of course, invest in all kinds of businesses, but I only invest
in the kinds of people that I think I can make money with.
I judge the entrepreneur.
It's pretty simple.
I look at the entrepreneur and
I think it's a great entrepreneur.
It's great business.
It always is.
But if you were starting over again in 2025,
what industry would you get into in today's world?
Let's say somebody they're coming out of school.
What industry would you get into in 2025?
Probably not the smartest industry to decide this
way, but I would decide on something I loved.
When?
When you have a business,
you're going to have a business.
When you have a passion for your
business or your product, you always do well.
So I would go in the flower business.
I've never been in the flower business.
I'd like to give it a hand.
I like that.
Do you?
Yeah.
I'll give you free flowers.
I'll take them happily.
You're known for spotting winning entrepreneurs.
Yes.
What's the number one trait that you look for in somebody,
a founder, that tells you that person's going to be successful?
You want to invest in them.
Somebody who's going to get it back up.
The only difference between good people and phenomenal
people is the ability to get back up.
So I'm always looking for that trait.
If I have that trait and that guy's got fire
in his belly or that girl has fire in her belly,
I've got a winner.
Is that innate, do you think?
Or can you develop that over time?
Or do you think that you're
either born with it or you're not?
I think it can be developed or exaggerated.
But I think a lot of
it is you're born with it.
Not everybody's a salesman.
You have to be a salesman to be an entrepreneur.
You have to sell your product.
You have to be a salesman.
You have to judge people well.
You have to make the right calls.
You have to have a good acumen for business.
There's a lot that goes into being an entrepreneur.
It's not born with a lot of people.
Was there an investment you made that surprised you?
Oh, yeah.
Tell me the story.
I bought a 12-unit motel in the countryside.
I actually bought it for
my ex-husband, which was a mistake.
He did nothing with it.
But the people had positioned
it as a great rent roll,
a nice, juicy rent roll.
Once I got in there as the owner,
I found out no one had
paid their rents in two years.
I buried it one year later with a bulldozer.
And it was the right thing to do.
I lost some money.
Goodbye, money.
I never made that mistake again.
So you've lost some money before.
I always lose money.
Who cares?
It's all a long game.
It's like, what you get in the end,
what you do in the meantime,
how much fun you could have.
Nah.
The winning and losing the
money is not the important part.
It's having the fun getting to go up and down.
Up and down.
It's really a blast.
What city would you go to in today's world
if you were starting your first business?
Probably Pittsburgh.
Why Pittsburgh?
Pittsburgh is great right now.
Pittsburgh is like a young New York.
It's got all young people, well-educated.
It's got tons of businesses moving in.
A lot of medical moving in there.
A lot of technology is taking over the town.
And it has a friendly government.
They love landlords.
That's who you want to be if you're a landlord.
Was there ever a time
that you were doubted in business?
Oh, come on.
What's my middle name?
Doubt is part of it.
Yeah, doubted from the very beginning.
I was doubted by the old
boy network, the rich guys who own
all the businesses.
It's a talent.
No women were in the field.
You have to appreciate that.
But that was to my advantage.
But they didn't want me in that old boys club.
But I got in the old boys club.
I was doubted by Donald
Trump when I sold his biggest
property he ever sold.
And he said, you'll never see
a penny of that $4 million
commission.
He doubted my ability to assume and win the commission.
I was doubted by Mark Burnett saying
I wasn't going to get the seat on Shark Tank.
And I wrote him, told him exactly why
I was going to be
the best girl in that seat.
You have to stand up for yourself.
The minute you have doubt,
you should use it for motivation
and push ahead.
Because it actually does give you motivation
if you look at it the right way.
That was incredible.
Yeah.
You're a schmoozer.
Get that in the tape.
And you have pretty eyes.
I could see why Shaquille was into you.
I appreciate that.
How important is it to choose the right life partner?
How important is that decision?
It's the most important call you'll ever make.
When you have a good life partner,
when you have a good business partner,
you double your chances of success.
Why would you go through life with the wrong partner?
It's no fun.
I almost did that with my first husband.
What happened?
I decided to leave.
I pulled out of my Porsche
one day and said, see ya, baby.
See ya.
Yeah.
What was, I guess, the biggest red flag
that you saw from that first marriage
that you kind of took on with you after that?
And maybe to kind of give that advice to somebody
that they're starting to date in today's world, right?
You kind of have that experience.
But what's a red flag and a partner that?
We never fought.
We never spoke honestly.
And he had a little
too much to drink most nights.
Bad.
I saw him as an alcoholic 10 years later,
which is what happened.
And we never talked.
Not really talked.
You have to talk to somebody.
You need a soul mate in your corner.
You know, you just need that soul mate.
For the bad times, my
husband's a pain in the neck.
But he's strong.
He's short grade in the bad times.
You got to find somebody
that's part of the solution, not
the problem.
Well, that would be a nice way to do.
But very often, they don't feel like the solution.
They just feel like a pain in the ass.
But you stick with it and see where it goes.
Right.
How old are you now?
How what?
25 years old.
Yeah.
So if you're not laughing at me, are you?
No, no.
I believe you.
OK, good.
I thought you were laughing.
I thought I saw a smile.
Definitely not.
But if you were to go back in time,
when you were coming out of school, right,
if you were to go back
in time and have a conversation
with your 20-year-old self, what's the best advice you'd
tell to your younger self?
I would have told myself that all
the F's and D's that I got
in school didn't amount to anything,
that all you really needed
to do is use your mouth
or use what asset you had to get ahead.
I would have told myself not to be so scared.
But in a way, I was
so scared it probably helped me succeed,
because the most insecure people are usually
the biggest businesses.
They're not really healthy.
So you weren't a great student in school?
Oh, no.
But I was charming.
The report my parents always got was, she's so nice,
but she's not very smart.
I'm actually not very nice.
Yeah.
I'm not very nice, and I am very smart.
I've learned.
But you're an expert communicator, though.
And let's say somebody, they don't
have a lot of credibility.
Maybe they don't have an established family
or great relationships.
How can somebody start leveraging their communication
skills to start getting in front of the right people?
Well, you have the advantage of being yourself.
Nobody's putting pressure on you to be somebody else.
You can be authentic to yourself.
And you can communicate in your own style
and decide exactly what direction you want to go in.
You're free, free as a bird.
I'm so thankful I didn't have affluent parents.
I was free at 18 getting out of that house,
quitting my job as a waitress and starting a business.
I mean, a rich kid couldn't do that.
You know, they think, what will people think of me?
Or maybe not get the
job as a waitress or whatever.
I had none of that.
I could do whatever I wanted.
I was a whole person when I was very young.
And your last message to somebody
watching this right now, trying to become Barbara Corcoran
wealthy in today's world.
How can somebody become a multimillionaire
in today's world?
Give them one last nugget, one last gem
to take with them from this interview.
This was incredible.
I would say be yourself.
You have to authentically be yourself.
People know the difference.
The minute I became myself
and stopped with the fancy hair
and started not to be
the fancy lady to fit in,
I was like, I'm going to start my business soon.
And it's always been true.
Everyone likes the authentic, real deal.
You've got to be yourself.
Build on what you have.
If you were to start from zero and you
had one year to make a million dollars
and your life depended on it, what would you do?
I wouldn't think I would
make a million dollars a year.
Honestly, I would sell apples on the corner
and make about $50,000 in the first month
and build from there.
You got amazing advice.
Thank you so much for your time.
I hope so.
I'm not going to hug you like Shaquille did.
See him competing?
All right, let me hug you.
Let me hug you.
Thank you.
That was excellent.
Yeah, that was incredible.
That's it actually looks.
Does it?
Yeah.
You might need to slow down.
No, you don't have to slow down.
That's the charm of it.
It moves quicker.
You know what the other charm is?
I don't know if you got my message yesterday.
You had the best questions.
You gave it thought.
You know, I get questions that
say all shit all the time.
They're all redundant.
You're not that way.
You've got your fresh questions.
That's what keeps your podcast great.
Thank you so much.
It's not called a podcast, but whatever it is.
It's just different because, I mean, it's like,
it's its own thing.
I think it's one of a kind, you know?
Yeah, but you probably tailor your questions
to exactly who you're interviewing.
Most people don't bother.
They have their questions.
And they kind of say, what else can I ask?
No, it was clear you gave it thought.
I said, whoa, these are good questions.
Thank you so much.
I appreciate that.
They work hard.
Nothing's wrong with over preparing, right?
Absolutely.
Guys, this interview with Barbara
was one of my favorite videos that I've ever done,
from start to finish, from talking about real estate
to finance to investing to entrepreneurship.
She was incredible.
So I need you guys to do
me a favor and like and subscribe
for amazing content I've got coming every single week
at the School of Podcasting.
I'm going to be doing a lot of hard knocks.
And like I said earlier, if
you are not a member yet
of my entrepreneur community, the number one community
in the entire world for business owners and entrepreneurs,
you are missing out because
you can join for free today
by going down to the link
in the description of this video.
And like I said, guys,
the reason why it's the biggest
and number one community for business owners
in the entire world is because every single week,
the people that join you
have the ability to get mentored
from the millionaires and the billionaires
that I interview on this channel every single week.
So come in and join.
If you could hop on a
live call and ask a specific question
to an entrepreneur like Barbara
and the most successful business owners, guys,
in a ton of different industries.
So come in and join
today for free and get mentored
by the most successful people in the entire world
and watch your life change.
I can't wait to see you on the inside.
Like I said, go down
to the link in the description
of this video to join the School of Mentors today.
And with that being said, I'll
see you in the next video.